https://www.sharetrails.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which we, BlueRibbon Coalition/ShareTrail. collects, uses, maintains and discloses personal information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the websites www.leeforsenate.com and all other websites owned and operated by BlueRibbon Coalition/ShareTrails (collectively, the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by BlueRibbon Coalition/ShareTrails by or through the Site.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the Site, subscribe to a newsletter or blog, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, mobile number, credit card information, employer, and occupation. Users may, however, visit our site without submitting such personal information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only to the extent such information is voluntarily submitted to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. A User’s web browser places cookies on the User’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about that User. A User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert the User when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
BlueRibbon Coalition/ShareTrails collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:
To personalize User experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To Improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our Site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactions and provide services
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order to respond to or provide services or products that were ordered. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to process payments, respond or provide the service or products.
To send periodic emails or texts
If User decides to opt-in to, or not opt-out from, our mailing list, they will receive emails or texts that may include news, updates, requests for donations, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails or texts, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or the User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt, and we use service providers who have adopted, appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchanged between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We may disclose or otherwise sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to third parties in our reasonable discretion. Some examples include, but are not limited to, specific campaigns, specific candidates or the national Republican Party. We may also share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, affiliates and advertisers.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be inaccurate and constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interacting with any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
BlueRibbon Coalition/ShareTrails has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email if we have your email address. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are handling the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, you are not permitted to use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, including a request to opt-out of our use of your personal information, please contact us at:
Mailing Address:
PO Box 5449
Pocatello, ID 83202
208-237-1008
Search for:
Recent Posts
#GivingTuesday – Support Us as We Fight for You
Keep Adventure Alive in Trail Canyon
Tell Congress, “No Lame Duck Wilderness”
BlueRibbon Coalition Supports BLM’s Rejection of SUWA’s San Rafael Desert Travel Plan Appeal
Keep the San Rafael Desert Open
